{
    "Arrested_development_why_the_world’s_poorest_are_being_left_behind": [
        [
            "The Economist",
            "WORK_OF_ART"
        ],
        [
            "September 2000",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "UN",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "New York",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "the United Nations Millennium Declaration",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "the new millennium",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "The United States",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Bill Clinton",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "one",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "189",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "eight",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "2015",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "the Millennium Development Goals",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "less than $1.25",
            "MONEY"
        ],
        [
            "more than half",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "the UN Development Program",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "15 years later",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "almost half",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "almost half",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "2015",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "17",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "70",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "Ukraine",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "the Middle East",
            "LOC"
        ],
        [
            "2015",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Money Talks",
            "WORK_OF_ART"
        ],
        [
            "Economist",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "weekly",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "New York",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Mike Bird",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "New York",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Alice Fowlwood",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "London",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Tom Lee Devlin",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "First",
            "ORDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "The 21st century",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "the first 15 years of the century",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "the Gates Foundation",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "the Ukraine war",
            "EVENT"
        ],
        [
            "One",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "Tom",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Mike",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "New York",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "last night",
            "TIME"
        ],
        [
            "New York",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "730",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "Mike",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "New York",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Alice",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "the end of the week",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "New York",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "the UN General Assembly",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "a few days",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "730",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "New York",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "79th",
            "ORDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "the United Nations General Assembly",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "today",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "UN",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "the two days",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "17",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "193",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "UN",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "September 2015",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "the 9 years",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "The first decade or so of the 21st century",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "the 9 years",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Mac",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Kerian Richmond-Jones",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Kerian",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Africans",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Africans",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "2022",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "1970",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "billion",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "2000",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "billion",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "World Bank",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "2.15",
            "MONEY"
        ],
        [
            "50 years ago",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "today",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "The 21st century",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "the first 15 years of the century",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "1.08 billion",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "only 60 million",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "the last 10 years",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "the East Asia",
            "LOC"
        ],
        [
            "Asia",
            "LOC"
        ],
        [
            "Africa",
            "LOC"
        ],
        [
            "50 years ago",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Tiley",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Mike",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "China",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "East Asia",
            "LOC"
        ],
        [
            "today",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Africa",
            "LOC"
        ],
        [
            "the Middle East",
            "LOC"
        ],
        [
            "Latin America",
            "LOC"
        ],
        [
            "Southeast Asia",
            "LOC"
        ],
        [
            "India",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "first",
            "ORDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "the last 50 years",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "second",
            "ORDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "Africa",
            "LOC"
        ],
        [
            "2000",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "the last 20 years",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "first",
            "ORDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "the 21st century",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "a golden decade",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "the early 21st century",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Africa",
            "LOC"
        ],
        [
            "Latin America",
            "LOC"
        ],
        [
            "the Middle East",
            "LOC"
        ],
        [
            "Southeast Asia",
            "LOC"
        ],
        [
            "2015",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "2020",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "the past 50 years",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Africa",
            "LOC"
        ],
        [
            "the Middle East",
            "LOC"
        ],
        [
            "Latin America",
            "LOC"
        ],
        [
            "first",
            "ORDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "the 2000s",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "the World Bank",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "UN",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Carian",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Carian",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "the Gates Foundation",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "2000",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Bill Gates",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Melinda French",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "$58 billion",
            "MONEY"
        ],
        [
            "US",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Warren Buffett",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Mark Susman",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Mark",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "One",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "the first year",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "COVID",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "INF",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "the World Bank",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "the United States",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "60",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "two",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "One",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "Ukraine",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Africa",
            "LOC"
        ],
        [
            "Europe",
            "LOC"
        ],
        [
            "Ukraine",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Ukraine",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "third",
            "ORDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "the Gates Foundation",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "One",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "the last five years",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "AI",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "one",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "Davos",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "the United Nations General Assembly",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "the last 25 years",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Gavi",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "the early 2000s",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "the United Kingdom",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "the United States",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "one",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "70",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "the World Bank",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "the Gates Foundation",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Mark",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "one",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "the first two years",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Mark",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Tom Alice",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Mark",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Mark",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "500 million dollars",
            "MONEY"
        ],
        [
            "Africa",
            "LOC"
        ],
        [
            "the Gates Foundation",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "the Gates Foundation",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Mark",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Africa",
            "LOC"
        ],
        [
            "one",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "recent years",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Mark",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Gavi",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "the years",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "2015",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Paul Collier",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Oxford University's Blavatinics School of Government",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "2007",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "The Bottom Billion",
            "WORK_OF_ART"
        ],
        [
            "earlier this year",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "the early 2000s",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "2015",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "a golden decade",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "about 2003",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "2003 through to 2014",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "2014",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Lewis",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "first",
            "ORDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "First",
            "ORDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "Lewis",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "One",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "The Left Behind",
            "WORK_OF_ART"
        ],
        [
            "One",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "Lewis",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "the last 15 to 20 years",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "One",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "two",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "the International Monetary Fund",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "the World Bank",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "first",
            "ORDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "the research department",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Joe Stiglitz",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "the world bank",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "two",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "one",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "one",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "one",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "The World Bank",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "one",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "IMF",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "the World Bank",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Paul",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Alice",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Tom",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Paul Collier",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "14",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "20th",
            "ORDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "Hyde Park",
            "LOC"
        ],
        [
            "14 years old",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "YouTube",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Lewis",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Korea",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Taiwan",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "China",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "eight",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "30 years",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "30 years",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Vietnam",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Philippines",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Morocco",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Paul",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Angola",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "the last 300 years",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Kerian",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "recent decades",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "the week",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Tom",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "the week",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "200%",
            "PERCENT"
        ],
        [
            "the past six years",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Tom",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "this week",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "week",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "the week",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "a quarter",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "six",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "Jekyll Island",
            "LOC"
        ],
        [
            "Georgia",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "my holiday last week",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Rockefellers",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "J.P. Morgan",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "six",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "1910",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "the Federal Reserve",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "the Federal Reserve",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Jekyll",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "about 20 years",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "one",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "the Federal Reserve",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Georgia",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "England",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "about 300 years",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "One",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "Europe",
            "LOC"
        ],
        [
            "the week",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "139",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "72",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Japanese",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "this week",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "160",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "earlier in the year",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Japan",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Fed",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Japan",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "162",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "30 years",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "30 years",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "500",
            "MONEY"
        ],
        [
            "Tokyo",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Uniclo",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Mark Sussman",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Paul Collier",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Money Talks",
            "WORK_OF_ART"
        ],
        [
            "Today",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Marie Kiworth",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Dan Asher",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Tingli Lim",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Hannah Marigno",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Mike Bird",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Alice Foward",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Tom Lee Devlin",
            "PERSON"
        ]
    ],
    "A_key_Keystone_the_race_for_Pennsylvania": [
        [
            "The Economist Mississippi",
            "WORK_OF_ART"
        ],
        [
            "Indiana",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Louisiana",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Florida",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Ohio",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "East Potomac Park",
            "LOC"
        ],
        [
            "Washington",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "D.C.",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "50",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "the White House",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Pennsylvania Avenue",
            "FAC"
        ],
        [
            "Pennsylvania",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Philadelphia",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "D.C.",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Pennsylvania Avenue",
            "FAC"
        ],
        [
            "the White House",
            "FAC"
        ],
        [
            "Donald Trump",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Carmela Harris",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "the White House",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Pennsylvania",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "19",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "32 days",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "2024",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "John Prado",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Chex",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "one",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "American",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Today",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Pennsylvania",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Pennsylvania",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Economist",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "three",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "Commonwealth",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Pennsylvania",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "November",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "this week",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Keystone",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "the last few weeks",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Charlotte Howard",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Idris Calune",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Pennsylvania",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Charlotte",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "New York",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Eric Adams",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "New York",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "DC",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "80s",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Idris",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Washington",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Washington",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Pittsburgh",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "many years ago",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "one",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "Art Deco",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Pennsylvania",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Pennsylvania",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "this time of year",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Eric",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Charlotte",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Eastern Pennsylvania",
            "LOC"
        ],
        [
            "third",
            "ORDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "an hour",
            "TIME"
        ],
        [
            "Philadelphia",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "about two hours",
            "TIME"
        ],
        [
            "New York",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Democratic",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Pennsylvania",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Philadelphia",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Northampton County",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Christopher Borrick",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Mule",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Berg College",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Pennsylvania",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Pennsylvania",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Philadelphia",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "one",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "Democratic",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Pennsylvania",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "the United States",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Pittsburgh",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Harrisburg",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Scranton",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Eury",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Pennsylvania",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Pennsylvania",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Midwestern",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Atlantic",
            "LOC"
        ],
        [
            "Pennsylvania",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Joe Biden",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Harris",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Harris",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "the Democratic Party",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Pennsylvania",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "late June",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "early July",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Biden",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Democrats",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "about three or four",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "Pennsylvania",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Harris",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Pennsylvania",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "2020",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Biden",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Trump",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "half",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "four years earlier",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Harris",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Biden",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "the Democratic Coalition",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "2020",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Biden",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "early summer",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "One",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "Pennsylvania",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Pennsylvania",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Lehigh Valley",
            "LOC"
        ],
        [
            "Harris",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "95%",
            "PERCENT"
        ],
        [
            "Republican",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "95%",
            "PERCENT"
        ],
        [
            "Democrat",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "5%",
            "PERCENT"
        ],
        [
            "Donald Trump",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Philadelphia",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Democratic",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "just a few weeks",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "election day",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Pennsylvania",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "a weekend",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Democrats",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Republicans",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Trump",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Trump",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "daily",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "several few days",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Charlotte",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "six",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "2024",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "seven",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "North Carolina",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Pennsylvania",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "19",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "Georgia",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "North Carolina's",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "16",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Trump",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Pennsylvania",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Biden",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Pennsylvania",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "one",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "Georgia",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Pennsylvania",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "late September",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Groups",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "more than $138 million",
            "MONEY"
        ],
        [
            "Pennsylvania",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "more than 50%",
            "PERCENT"
        ],
        [
            "Michigan",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Philadelphia",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Philadelphia",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "the Lehigh Valley",
            "LOC"
        ],
        [
            "Hispanic",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "the Lehigh Valley",
            "LOC"
        ],
        [
            "Northampton",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Allentown",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Bethlehem Steel",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Pittsburgh",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "second",
            "ORDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "Pennsylvania",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Republican",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Erie",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Erie",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Pennsylvania",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "the Great Lake",
            "LOC"
        ],
        [
            "Harris",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Trump",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "last weekend",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Butler",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Pennsylvania",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "this weekend",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Trump",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Harris",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Pennsylvania",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "three",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "ten",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "Trump",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Pennsylvania",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Georgia",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "North Carolina",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "270",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "Harris",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Pennsylvania",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Michigan",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Wisconsin",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Nebraska",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "270",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "Pennsylvania",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Pennsylvania",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "America",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "20%",
            "PERCENT"
        ],
        [
            "Pennsylvania",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "65 years",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "17.7%",
            "PERCENT"
        ],
        [
            "18%",
            "PERCENT"
        ],
        [
            "America",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Pennsylvania",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "about $74,000",
            "MONEY"
        ],
        [
            "78,000",
            "MONEY"
        ],
        [
            "America",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Pennsylvania",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "the electoral college",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Harris",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "50",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "Charlotte",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Pennsylvania",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Pennsylvania",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Pennsylvania",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "North Ampton",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Allentown",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "the Lehigh Valley",
            "LOC"
        ],
        [
            "Obama",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Trump",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Biden",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Democrats",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "North Ampton",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Bethlehem",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Bethlehem",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Bethlehem",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "English",
            "LANGUAGE"
        ],
        [
            "US",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Pittsburgh",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Adrice",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Nippon",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Japanese",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Biden",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "US",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Nippon",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Bethlehem",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Pittsburgh",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "North Ampton",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Pittsburgh",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Biden",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "daily",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Biden",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "one",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "Democratic",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Democrats",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Democrats",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Trump",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Biden",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Commonwealth",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Trump",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Charlottes",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Idris",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "this week",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "the year",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "the Middle East",
            "LOC"
        ],
        [
            "the past year",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Japanese",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Shiba",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "American",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Pennsylvania",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "eighth",
            "ORDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "New York",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "New Jersey",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "the Republican party",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "the cross street",
            "FAC"
        ],
        [
            "Adams and Biden street",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Scranton",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Pennsylvania",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Joe Biden",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Pennsylvania",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "eighth",
            "ORDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "Pennsylvania",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "eighth",
            "ORDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "Obama",
            "LOC"
        ],
        [
            "Trump",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "2012",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Barack Obama",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Joe Biden",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "12",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "2016",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Donald Trump",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "9.6",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "2020",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Donald Trump",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "0.9",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "Kamala Harris",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Tim Wolts",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Pennsylvania",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Joe Biden's",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "2020",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Hillary Clinton's",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "2016",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "America",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Trump",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Donald Trump",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "November 5",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Pennsylvania",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "eighth",
            "ORDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "Donald Trump",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Democrat",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "the House of Representatives",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Republicans",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Lu Barletta",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Pennsylvania",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "decades",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "One",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "today",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Republican",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "34 year old",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Rob Bresnerhan",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Pennsylvania",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Bresnerhan",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Joe Biden",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "nearly 100%",
            "PERCENT"
        ],
        [
            "95%",
            "PERCENT"
        ],
        [
            "Eastern Pennsylvania",
            "LOC"
        ],
        [
            "Two days ago",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Bresnerhan",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Republican",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Wednesday",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "night",
            "TIME"
        ],
        [
            "Donald Trump",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Kamala Harris",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Trump",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Republican",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Luzern",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "one",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "2016",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "the Republican Party",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "the Democrat Party",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "millions",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "Jesus",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Mindela",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Rose Supparks",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Lincoln",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Fitzgerald",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "America",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Democrat",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Republican",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Congress",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Republican",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Pennsylvania",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "2020",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Hillary",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Democrat",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "first",
            "ORDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "CIA",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "FBI",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Videos",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Trump",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Idris",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "TJ Fitzgerald",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Hillary Clinton",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Trump",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Springfield",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "America",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "about two weeks ago",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Hillary Clinton",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "MSNBC",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Russians",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "2016",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Americans",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Russians",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "the United States",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Pennsylvania",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "One",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "Trump",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "JD Vance",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Congress",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "John",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Congress",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Trump",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Rob Brothers",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "four",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "Republicans",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Trump",
            "WORK_OF_ART"
        ],
        [
            "Republican",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Congress",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Republican",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Pennsylvania",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "2020",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Democrats",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Donald Trump",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Trump",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Kamala Harris",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Kamala Harris",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Kamala Harris",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Pennsylvania",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Adrice",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Pennsylvania",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Republican",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Republican",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Pennsylvania",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "2020",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Kamala Harris",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "2020",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Rudy Giuliani",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "America",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Pennsylvania",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "American",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Idris",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Trump",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Harris",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Pennsylvania",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Pennsylvania",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "election day",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Republicans",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "one",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "PA8",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "Republican",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Idris",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Western Pennsylvania",
            "LOC"
        ],
        [
            "Idris",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Pennsylvania",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Pittsburgh",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "a fun summer",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "One",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "first",
            "ORDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "Harris",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Bri Erskin",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Bellevue",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Pennsylvania",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "a rainy day",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Bellevue",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Main Area Pittsburgh",
            "FAC"
        ],
        [
            "one",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "Harris",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Harris",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "American",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Karmala",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Democrat",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Chris Delusio",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Pennsylvania",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "17th",
            "ORDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "Pittsburgh",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Joe Biden",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "2020",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Democrats",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "the Union Hall after",
            "FAC"
        ],
        [
            "Delusio",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Donald Trump",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Constitution",
            "LAW"
        ],
        [
            "January 6th",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Trump",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Republicans",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "these days",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "America",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "the Democratic Party",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Democrats",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "about than say",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "2020",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Joe Biden",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Western Pennsylvania",
            "LOC"
        ],
        [
            "Democrats",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Western Pennsylvania",
            "LOC"
        ],
        [
            "two",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "Allegheny County",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Pittsburgh",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "17th",
            "ORDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "Eri",
            "LOC"
        ],
        [
            "Eri",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "one",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "only two",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "Northampton County",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Donald Trump",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "2016",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Joe Biden",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "2020",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Eri",
            "LOC"
        ],
        [
            "last weekend",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Jeff Bloodworth",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "American",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Ganon University",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Eri",
            "LOC"
        ],
        [
            "the Great Lake",
            "LOC"
        ],
        [
            "Turkish",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Pennsylvania",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "20%",
            "PERCENT"
        ],
        [
            "Eri",
            "LOC"
        ],
        [
            "African American",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Eri",
            "LOC"
        ],
        [
            "Republicans",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Trump",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Democrat",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Democrats",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Harris",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "the Eri County Democratic Party",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Democratic Party",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "the Eri County Democratic Party",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Democrats",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Kamala Harris",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Kyle Faust",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Harris",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "eight",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "the Eri County Democratic Party",
            "LOC"
        ],
        [
            "Democrat",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Trump",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Perkinsville",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Democrat",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Trump",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "16",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "Joe Biden",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "20",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "Donald Trump",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Pennsylvania",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Charlotte",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "only two",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "Donald Trump",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Joe Biden",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "2022",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Pennsylvania",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "67",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "one",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "Pennsylvania",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Donald Trump",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Jeff",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "one",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "Trump",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Trump",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "America",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Harris",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Trump",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "democratic",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "today",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "John",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Adrie",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "two",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "Democrats",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Trump",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "the Biden years",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Harris",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Pittsburgh",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Democrats",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Americans",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Americans",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Harris",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Donald Trump",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Democrats",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Americans",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Hillary Clinton",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Pennsylvania",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Loco",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Scranton",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Joe Biden",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Biden",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Catholic",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Hillary",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "2016",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Harris",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Harris",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Democrats",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Trump",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Democrats",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Pennsylvania",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Latinos",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Harris",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Latino",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Pennsylvania",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Latinos",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Trump",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Dems",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Republicans",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "three",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "Wisconsin",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Michigan",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Pennsylvania",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Idris",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "African American",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Pennsylvania",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Philadelphia",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Pittsburgh",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Philadelphia",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "one",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "Democratic",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Philadelphia",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Philadelphia",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Democratic",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Philadelphia",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "African Americans",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Hispanic Americans",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Northwest",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Philadelphia",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Democrats",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Pennsylvania",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "election week",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "the Electoral College",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Pennsylvania",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "19",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "Electoral College",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "one",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "Pennsylvania",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Pennsylvania",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Iliad",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Pennsylvania",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Helen of Troy",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "thousand",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "one",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "two",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "Illinois",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Charlotte",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "New York",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Texas",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "two",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "Six",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "DC",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "three",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "North Dakota",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "South Dakota",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Alaska",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Wyoming",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Delaware",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Adres",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Vermont",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Charlotte",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "three",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "four",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "California",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "New York",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Texas",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "California",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Texas",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "New York",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Florida",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "California",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Texas",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Florida",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "New York",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "New York",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "New York",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "2020",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "this week",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Charlotte",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Adres",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Harriet Noble",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Stevie Hertz",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Margaret Howell",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Saul Rivers",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "one",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "Pennsylvania",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Steve",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Philadelphia",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Jeremy",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "next week's",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "China",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "next week",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "next week",
            "DATE"
        ]
    ],
    "A_new_prescription_Kathy_Willis_on_how_nature_can_improve_your_health": [
        [
            "The Economist Like",
            "WORK_OF_ART"
        ],
        [
            "London",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "The Economist Take",
            "WORK_OF_ART"
        ],
        [
            "Over 300 acres",
            "QUANTITY"
        ],
        [
            "the Royal Botanic Gardens",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Victorian",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "London",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "this week",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Kathy Willis",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "the University of Oxford",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "two",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "Botanic Garden",
            "FAC"
        ],
        [
            "Kathy",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Good Nature, Kathy",
            "WORK_OF_ART"
        ],
        [
            "Alok Jar",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Babbage",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Economist",
            "FAC"
        ],
        [
            "Today",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Kathy",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Babbage",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "two",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "the last five years",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Good Nature",
            "WORK_OF_ART"
        ],
        [
            "one",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "the last five years",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "20 minutes",
            "TIME"
        ],
        [
            "900,000",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "UK",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "first",
            "ORDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "calmer",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "first",
            "ORDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "Roger Orrick",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "two",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "First",
            "ORDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "second",
            "ORDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "Spain",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "2015",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Barcelona Institute for Global Health",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "2,500",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "8",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "1,500 years",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "three",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "the year",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "English",
            "LANGUAGE"
        ],
        [
            "Spanish",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "month",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "month",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "one",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "Australia",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "one",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "66",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "five minutes",
            "TIME"
        ],
        [
            "four",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "one minute",
            "TIME"
        ],
        [
            "Sweden",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "one",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "over 90 minutes",
            "TIME"
        ],
        [
            "every 10 minutes",
            "TIME"
        ],
        [
            "one",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "two",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "first",
            "ORDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "years ago",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Japanese",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Hinoe",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "three nights",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "three nights",
            "TIME"
        ],
        [
            "first",
            "ORDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "three nights",
            "TIME"
        ],
        [
            "second",
            "ORDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "first",
            "ORDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "2009",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "the past couple of years",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Oncology",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "cypress",
            "FAC"
        ],
        [
            "two hours",
            "TIME"
        ],
        [
            "seven days",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "first",
            "ORDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "first",
            "ORDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "the age of about three or four",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "the 93%",
            "PERCENT"
        ],
        [
            "Finland",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "the last two years",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "three",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "One",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "second",
            "ORDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "third",
            "ORDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "28 days",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "two",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "28 days",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "six weeks later",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "one",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "the United Nations",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "COP",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "last year",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "a hundred and eighty nine",
            "QUANTITY"
        ],
        [
            "those hundred and eighty nine",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "Hinokey",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "one",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "Copenhagen",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "eight months",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "half",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "ten weeks",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "two hour",
            "TIME"
        ],
        [
            "half",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "two hours",
            "TIME"
        ],
        [
            "these ten weeks",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "70%",
            "PERCENT"
        ],
        [
            "CBT",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "18 months later",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "two hours",
            "TIME"
        ],
        [
            "two",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "the Cue Gardens",
            "LOC"
        ],
        [
            "Britain",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "first",
            "ORDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "Botanic Gardens",
            "LOC"
        ],
        [
            "five years ago",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Kathy",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "the year",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "the Medical Journalist Association Awards",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "May 2023",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Jason Hoskin",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Nico Roefast",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Hannah Moreno",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Alok Jar",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "London",
            "GPE"
        ]
    ],
    "Ballot_box_bets_What_America's_election_means_for_investors": [
        [
            "The Economist",
            "WORK_OF_ART"
        ],
        [
            "2016",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Jane Street",
            "FAC"
        ],
        [
            "one",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "election night",
            "TIME"
        ],
        [
            "CNN",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Jane",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "hundreds",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "Sam Boutman",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "years",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Jane Street",
            "FAC"
        ],
        [
            "SPF",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "SPF",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "the Florida Panhandle",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Donald Trump",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "CNN",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Hillary Clinton",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Donald Trump",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Donald Trump",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Donald Trump",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "US",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Mexico",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Trump",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "CNN",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Trump",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Jane Street",
            "FAC"
        ],
        [
            "half a billion dollars",
            "MONEY"
        ],
        [
            "1am",
            "TIME"
        ],
        [
            "$300 million",
            "MONEY"
        ],
        [
            "trading day",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Trump",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "SPF",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "a few hours later",
            "TIME"
        ],
        [
            "Jane Street's",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "$300 million",
            "MONEY"
        ],
        [
            "Michael Lewis",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "SPF",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Money Talks",
            "WORK_OF_ART"
        ],
        [
            "Economist",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "weekly",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "this week",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Washington, DC",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Alice Forward",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "today",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "2024",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "First",
            "ORDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "Harris",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "four",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "seven or",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "Trump",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "three month",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Republican",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "White House",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "12 month",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Democrat",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "White House",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "this week",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Paul Listeners",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Simon Remidavitch",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Simon",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Alice",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Tom",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Mike",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Mike",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "week",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "US",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "week",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Trump",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Harris",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Trump",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "four years",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "2016",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Harris",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Biden",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "the past four years",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "today",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "four years",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "eight years ago",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "2016",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Trump",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "first",
            "ORDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "2020",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "the last four years",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "America",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "the past few years",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Fed",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "7%",
            "PERCENT"
        ],
        [
            "Trump",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Trump",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "America",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "trillions",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "Harris",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Americans",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Owen Winter",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Owen",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "first",
            "ORDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "Money Talks",
            "WORK_OF_ART"
        ],
        [
            "Joe Biden",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Kamala Harris",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Biden",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Trump",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "about three or four",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "Joe Biden",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Kamala Harris",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "the Democratic Party",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Democrats",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "the day",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Harris",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Trump",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Joe Biden's",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "today",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "four",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "Harris",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Democrats",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Trump",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Harris",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "four",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "seven or",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "Pennsylvania",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "one",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "270th",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "the electoral college",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Pennsylvania",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Harris",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "1.2",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "Pennsylvania",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Harris",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "today",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Harris",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "57%",
            "PERCENT"
        ],
        [
            "One",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "the White House",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Congress",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Harris",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "House",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Senate",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Donald Trump",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Democrats",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "House",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "the House of Representatives",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Republicans",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Harris",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "House",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Senate",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "this year",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Democrats",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Senate",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Senate",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Ohio",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Montana",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Republicans",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Texas",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Florida",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Democrats",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Senate",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Kamala Harris",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Republicans",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Senate",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Donald Trump",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Congress",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Owen",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Joe Saluzzi",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Themis Trading",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Joe",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Alice",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "2016",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Trump",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "the days",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "2016",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "50-50",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "Trump",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "four years",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "2024",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Trump",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Trump",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "2016",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Republicans",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Kamala Harris",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "democratic",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "years",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "the Supreme Court",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "six",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "Chevron",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Chevron",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "FTC",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "FCC",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "FCC",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Trump",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Harris",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Trump",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Trump",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Harris",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Trump",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "one",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "hundreds of billions of dollars",
            "MONEY"
        ],
        [
            "Trump",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "10 to 20%",
            "PERCENT"
        ],
        [
            "the 1920s",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "smooth haulie",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Biden-Harris",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "China",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Joe",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Alice",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Simon",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Jane Streets",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "one",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "Trump 1.0",
            "LAW"
        ],
        [
            "Basel III Endgame",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Trump",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Harris",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "EV",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Trump",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Alice",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Owen",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "first",
            "ORDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "Congress",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "one",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "Republican",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Senate",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "the White House",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Trump",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Harris",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Senate",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Joe Manchin",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Biden",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Trump",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "non-Maga",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Republican",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Susan Collins",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Maine",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Kamala Harris",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Democrat",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Joe Manchin",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Sherrod Brown",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Ohio",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Trump",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Joe",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Los",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "2016",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Trump",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "the second half",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Bar New Buweja",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "UBS",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Money Talks",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Alice Hayden",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "today",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "US",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "US",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "the last 100 years",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "years",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "an election year",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "about 1 to",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "election years",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "normal years",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "three month",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Republican",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "White House",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "12 month",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Democrat",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "White House",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "election years",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "the three month",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "the 12 month",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Republican",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "the White House",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "the White House",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Democrat",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Kamala Harris",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "12 month",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Democrat",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Republican",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Trump",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Trump",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Trump",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "2017",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Jobs Act",
            "LAW"
        ],
        [
            "21%",
            "PERCENT"
        ],
        [
            "15%",
            "PERCENT"
        ],
        [
            "Republican",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "2025 and 2026",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "about 19%",
            "PERCENT"
        ],
        [
            "2019",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Republican",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Democrat",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Republican",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Republican",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "one",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "Republicans",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "three",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "Congress",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Democrat",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Senate",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Republican",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "at least 60%",
            "PERCENT"
        ],
        [
            "21%",
            "PERCENT"
        ],
        [
            "28%",
            "PERCENT"
        ],
        [
            "Kamala Harris",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "American",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Republican",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "60%",
            "PERCENT"
        ],
        [
            "China",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "10%",
            "PERCENT"
        ],
        [
            "28%",
            "PERCENT"
        ],
        [
            "Democrat",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Congress",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Senate",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Republican",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "a three month",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "2016",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Trump",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "the day",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Alice",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "today",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "2016",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "jargon",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "2016",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Today",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "one",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "US",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "about 25",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "2016",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Democrat",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Republican",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "the Congressional Budgetary Office",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "CBO",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "$4 trillion",
            "MONEY"
        ],
        [
            "Fed",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "the 10 year",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Fed",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "thirdly",
            "ORDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "today",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "2016",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Today",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Trump",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "10%",
            "PERCENT"
        ],
        [
            "60%",
            "PERCENT"
        ],
        [
            "China",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "about three to four",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "three to four",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "between 2016 and 2020",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Republican",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Red Sweep",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "2016",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Kamala Harris",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Democrat",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Republican",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "2025",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "the White House",
            "FAC"
        ],
        [
            "Democrat",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "White House",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Congress",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Congress",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Democrat",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "White House",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "the last 18 months",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Fed",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Democrat",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Democrat",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Republican",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Trump",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Trump",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Democratic",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Alice",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Democrat",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Democrat",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Republican",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "US",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "first",
            "ORDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "today",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "about 235 years",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "US",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "27 trillion",
            "CARDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "another 27 trillion dollars",
            "MONEY"
        ],
        [
            "the next 10 years",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Benanki",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "the mid-2000s",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Democrat",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "an additional two trillion dollars",
            "MONEY"
        ],
        [
            "the next 10 years",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "as much as 4.1 to",
            "PERCENT"
        ],
        [
            "4.5 trillion dollars",
            "MONEY"
        ],
        [
            "US",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Bonnie",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Alice",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Simon",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Alice",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "the United States and America",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Trump",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Harris",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Trump",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Trump",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "second",
            "ORDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "Trump",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Biden",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "American",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "American",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Harris",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "almost every day",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "American",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "the last decade",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "2016",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Trump",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "America",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "China",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Biden",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "2020",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "America",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "American",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "American",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "2024",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Trump",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Harris",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "today",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "America",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Canadian",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "the United States of America",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "Bonnie",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Fed",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Fed",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Trump",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Fed",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Fed",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Trump",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "House",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Senate",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Fed",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Fed",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Fed",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "White House",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Trump",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "second",
            "ORDINAL"
        ],
        [
            "Trump",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "Trump versus Fed",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "America",
            "GPE"
        ],
        [
            "American",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "the week",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "Simon",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Money Talk's",
            "ORG"
        ],
        [
            "last week",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "the week before",
            "DATE"
        ],
        [
            "2%",
            "PERCENT"
        ],
        [
            "2%",
            "PERCENT"
        ],
        [
            "2%",
            "PERCENT"
        ],
        [
            "Japanese",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Mike",
            "PERSON"
        ],
        [
            "Japanese",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "Chinese",
            "NORP"
        ],
        [
            "10-year",
            "DATE"
